 let questions = [{
    "question": "What is HTML?",
    "option1": "HighText Markup Language",
    "option2": "HyperText Markup Language",
    "option3": "HyperText Made Lines",
    "option4": "HyperTax markup lines",
    "answer": "2"
},

{
    "question": "Which One is an HTML Extension?",
    "option1": ".css",
    "option2": ".js",
    "option3": ".html",
    "option4": ".hml",
    "answer": "3"
},

{
    "question": "Which HTML tag makes the text bold?",
    "option1": "<b>",
    "option2": "<a>",
    "option3": "<bl>",
    "option4": "<bd>",
    "answer": "1"
},

{
    "question": "Which HTML tag makes the text italic?",
    "option1": "<i>",
    "option2": "<italic>",
    "option3": "<it>",
    "option4": "<il>",
    "answer": "1"
},

{
    "question": "Which tag is used to define a line break",
    "option1": "<brr>",
    "option2": "<break>",
    "option3": "<br>",
    "option4": "<br>..</br>",
    "answer": "3"
},

{
    "question": "What does the <br> tag add to your webpage?",
    "option1": "Paragraph break",
    "option2": "Long break",
    "option3": "Line break",
    "option4": "None of the above",
    "answer": "3"
},

{
    "question": "Which of the following is a pragraph tag in HTML?",
    "option1": "<paragraph>...</paragraph>",
    "option2": "<p>...</p>",
    "option3": "<ul>...</ul>",
    "option4": "<pa>...</pa>",
    "answer": "2"
},
{
    "question": "All HTML tags are enclosed in?",
    "option1": "{ and }",
    "option2": "[ and ]",
    "option3": "( and )",
    "option4": "< and >",
    "answer": "4"
},
{
    "question": "The Body tag usually comes after the?",
    "option1": "HTML tag",
    "option2": "HEAD tag",
    "option3": "TITLE tag",
    "option4": "EM tag",
    "answer": "2"
},
{
    "question": "Which character represent the closing of a HTML tag?",
    "option1": "/",
    "option2": "+",
    "option3": "%",
    "option4": "!",
    "answer": "1"
},
{
    "question": "Which tag represent the start and end of a page?",
    "option1": "<body></body>",
    "option2": "<head></head>",
    "option3": "<title></title>",
    "option4": "<html></html>",
    "answer": "4"
},
{
    "question": "Which tag represent an unordered list?",
    "option1": "<li></li>",
    "option2": "<ul></ul>",
    "option3": "<ol></ol>",
    "option4": "<br>",
    "answer": "2"
},
{
    "question": "What does URL means?",
    "option1": "United Research Locator",
    "option2": "Uniform Research Locator",
    "option3": "Uniform Resource Locator",
    "option4": "United Refund Locator",
    "answer": "3"
},
{
    "question": "Which HTML tag produce the biggest heading?",
    "option1": "<h1>",
    "option2": "<h2>",
    "option3": "<h4>",
    "option4": "<h6>",
    "answer": "1"
},
{
    "question": "A normal webpage consist of?",
    "option1": "Body and Mind",
    "option2": "Body and Legs",
    "option3": "Head and Body",
    "option4": "Top and Bottom",
    "answer": "3"
}
    
]